Marcio Nogueira de Lima

46 years old

Married / (1 Son)

Contacts

Address:

Sarandi, Paraná. Brazil.

Phone:

+55 (44) 99930-2641

Emails:

marciolima76@hotmail.com

marciolima76.ml@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/marci o-lima-45077376/

Languages

Portuguese – Native Speaker English – C2 Italian – A1 Spanish – A1

Hobbies

- Reading
- Codding
- Languages
- Music

Summary: Working as a teacher of English since 2009, after returning from an experience in England, where lived for three years. With two graduations (Bilingual Executive Secretary and Licentiate teaching Portuguese-English) have also taught several subjects in technical courses (Administration and Accounting). In 2020, with the Pandemic, started working from home and became an online teacher of English and Portuguese. Also started learning Computer Science in order to increase his knoledges and to get more oportunitys of work.

Experiences

Teacher of English, 2023 –present.
DevEnglish – School of English for IT professionals

• Teacher of English, 2020 –2022.

New Age Academy – School of English (Callan Method on line).

• Teacher of English, 2015 – 2018.

MSI School - (New English Life - Oxford Method). Maringá - Paraná.

• Post Office Agent 2014 - present.

EBCT (Correios do Brasil)

• Teacher of English, 2013 - 2015.

Discovery Callan Method – English School, Maringá, Paraná.

 Teacher of Portuguese and English, 2010 - 2014. - Primary, Secundary and Professional Education School - Sarandi and Maringá, Paraná, Brazil.

Education

• Analisys and System Development

UniFCV. Maringá – Paraná – Brazil (2020 – 2023).

• Languages / Literature Graduation Course

Unicesumar, Maringá – Paraná - Brazil (2014 – 2017).

• Educational Formation in Teaching

UEM, Maringá - Paraná. - Brazil (2014)

• Postgraduated in Higher Education Teaching

Uniasselvi, Maringá- Paraná - Brazil (2012-2013).

• Graduated in Bilingual Executive Secretary

Unioeste, Toledo, Paraná - Brazil (1995-1998).

International Certifications

 Cambridge ESOL - University of Cambridge, Bracknell and Wokinghan College, England – UK (2006-2008).